[Music]
[Música]
My mother has
mi madre me ha
ruined my friendships and relationships. I see a
arruinado amistades relaciones veo a una
possessed mother. I feel like giving
madre endemoniada tengo ganas de darle
the public an explanation. They
una explicación al público tienen que
also need to know the B-side of
saber también la cara B de la historia
Sofia Suescun's story. They need to know. She
de Sofía suescun tienen que saberlo Ya
just went, eh, I mean, on this
acaba de ir eh o sea en el programa este
Friday's program, they're paying a lot, eh. And the mother has
de viernes pagan tocho eh Y la madre ha
posted a serious and urgent statement for
puesto comunicado serio y urgente para
all of Spain. I'm looking to live on a farm in
toda España Busco vivir en finca a
exchange for walking dogs, no. Or keep
cambio de paseos a perritos no O dar
company with a gentleman or lady, or something similar.
compañía a señor señora similar
Preferably Madrid or the north. I'm
preferentemente Madrid o el norte soy
nice, fun, and honest. I'll read you
simpática divertida y honrada os leeré
on Instagram. No, dude, this
por Instagram No pues cachón vaya esto
has to be all prepared, right? Javi.
tiene que estar todo preparado no Javi
What do you think? Don't you think this is even
tú qué opinas tú no crees que esto está
halfway prepared? I don't know what to tell you, I just do
medianamente preparado no sé qué decirte
n't know what to tell you because, of course. In
es que no sé qué decirte porque Claro En
part, yes, no, that's why I thought that the
parte sí no por eso Pensaba yo que el
main course was Sofia Suescun. No, but
plato gordo era sofí suescun no pero
of course, she's so crazy,
claro es que está tan como una cabra
so it could also be true, eh. I don't
entonces también podría ser verdad eh No
believe anything.
me creo nada